Dorothy Thompson Papers
Dorothy Thompson Papers
- Manuscripts
  - Manuscripts - general articles
    - Untitled articles with subject headings
      - The American revolution, original typescript (Box 102)
      - American war aims, original typescript (Box 102)
      - American war production, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Anti-Billboard campaign, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Atomic bomb, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Atomic warfare, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Austrian neutrality, typescript copy; 15 items (Box 102)
      - Battle of Leningrad, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Ernest Bevin, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - British Labor government, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Hermann Budzislawski, typescript copy; 5 items (Box 102)
      - Christmas, 1945, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Churchill's speech, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Coal strike, 1946, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Common man, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Communism, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Communism versus democracy, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Constitutional reform, holograph--Carbon; 7 items (Box 102)
      - Dispossessed minorities, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Domestic politics, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Domestic policy, original typescript; 3 items (Box 102)
      - Economic problems, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Education, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Eisenhower, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Emotional security, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Egypt, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - European economics, holograph (Box 102)
      - European peace, typescript copy; 7 items (Box 102)
      - Father, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Filene's Automatic Bargain Basement, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Food distribution, holograph (Box 102)
      - Foreign policy costs, holograph (Box 102)
      - Freedom House: Jan Masaryk, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Full Employment Bill, typescript copy; 6 items (Box 102)
      - German army, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - German de-Nazification, original typescript (Box 102)
      - German Social Democratic Movement, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - German surrender, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Germany: a look backward, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Germany: military governors, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Germany: Nazism, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Germany: nine years later, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Germany: prospects for victory, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Herschel Grynszpan, original typescript; 12 items (Box 102)
      - Heydrich, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Hitler, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Max Hölz, holograph (Box 102)
      - Hungary, original typescript; 4 items (Box 102)
      - Involvement, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Isolationism, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Isolationism, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Japan's war tactics, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Jewish question, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Jewish question, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Jewish question, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Maxim Kopf, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Korea, original typescript; 17 items (Box 102)
      - Labor and the economy, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Labor problems, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Liberalism, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Lindbergh, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Listen, Hans, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Norman Littell, original typescript (Box 102)
      - London Peace Conference, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - London Peace Conference, typescript copy; 9 items (Box 102)
      - Draja Mikhailovich, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Molotoff's Peace, original typescript (Box 102)
      - The Morgenthau Plan, typescript copy; 13 items (Box 102)
      - National Socialism, German style, original typescript (Box 102)
      - The Nazis, typescript (Box 102)
      - Nazism, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Needs of mankind, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Martin Niemoeller, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - The nineteenth century, original typescript; 6 items (Box 102)
      - Peace, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Peace conferences, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Peace: V-E Day, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Poland, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - The political crisis, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - The Potsdam Declaration, original typescript (Box 102)
      - The presidency, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Price controls, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Price controls: O.P.A., typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Prices of farm products, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Prince Otto of Habsburg, typescript copy; 12 items (Box 102)
      - Radio, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Refugee reform, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Republican Party, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Review of "Germany and Europe", typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Roosevelt: anniversary of his death, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Roosevelt: my vote, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Russians in Bonn, original typescript; 9 items (Box 102)
      - Edna St. Vincent Millay, original typescript (Box 102)
      - S.E.C., original typescript (Box 102)
      - Science, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Security, holograph (Box 102)
      - Stalin and Hitler, original typescript; 7 items (Box 102)
      - Teaching, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Teheran Conference, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Toscanini: introduction, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Toscanini: biography, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Trade dispute, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Trieste, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Twin Farms, typescript copy; 9 items (Box 102)
      - Unemployment, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Vermont, holograph (Box 102)
      - Wagner-Murray-Dingell Bill, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War, original typescript (Box 102)
      - War guilt, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Washington Memorial, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Sumner Wells, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Burton Wheeler, original typescript (Box 102)
      - Woman Suffrage Campaign, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Women, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - World peace, typescript copy; 16 items (Box 102)
      - Yusif El-Bandak, original typescript; 1 item (Box 102)
      - Zionism, typescript copy (Box 102)
      - Karl Zuckmayer, typescript copy; 4 items (Box 102)
      - Miscellaneous typescripts, incomplete; 5 items (Box 102)
  - Manuscripts - newspaper articles
    - Austro-Hungarian problems, typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Back to Blood and Iron", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Ex-Premier to be Tried for Murder", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Foreign Loans Are Only Morphine Injections", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - German nationalist papers, typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Habsburg Partisans Plan Coup d'Etat", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - Hungarian bombings, typescript copy (Box 102)
    - Hungarian elections, typescript copy (Box 102)
    - Hungary: conditions, typescript copy (Box 102)
    - Hungary: finances, original typescript (Box 102)
    - Hungary: Ulysses Grant Smith, original typescript (Box 102)
    - "Karl's Departure Forestalls Putch", original typescript (Box 102)
    - "The Market of the Profiteers", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Opera Bouffe in Budapest", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Russian Refugees", original typescript (Box 102)
    - "Strange Rats in Vienna Sewers", typescript copy (Box 102)
    - "Succession States Move Toward Understanding", original typescript (Box 102)
    - Vienna: musical events, typescript copy; 21 items (Box 102)
  - Manuscripts - speeches, 1929-1943
    - America, original typescript; 7 items (Box 103)
    - Changing world and future world order, original typescript; 2 items (Box 103)
    - China, original typescript; 2 items (Box 103)
    - Christian spirit, original typescript; 2 items (Box 103)
    - Commencement addresses, original typescript; 3 items (Box 103)
    - Constitution, original typescript; 5 items (Box 103)
    - Current events, original typescript; 1 item (Box 103)
    - Democracy, original typescript; 13 items (Box 103)
    - Education, original typescript; 4 items (Box 103)
    - Europe, original typescript; 8 items (Box 103)
    - Ralph E. Flanders, original typescript; 1 item (Box 103)
    - Foreign policy, original typescript; 6 items (Box 103)
    - Freedom, original typescript; 9 items (Box 103)
    - Germany, original typescript; 7 items (Box 103)
    - Government and propaganda, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 103)
    - Isolationism, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 103)
    - Jewish question, original typescript; 5 items (Box 103)
    - Journalism, holograph; 13 items (Box 103)
    - Latin America, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 104)
    - League of Nations, original typescript; 1 item (Box 104)
    - Liberty, original typescript; 1 item (Box 104)
    - Thomas Mann, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 104)
    - National Socialism, original typescript; 1 item (Box 104)
    - Neutrality, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 104)
    - Peace movements, original typescript; 1 item (Box 104)
    - Poland, original typescript; 4 items (Box 104)
    - Russia, original typescript; 5 items (Box 104)
    - Social responsibility, original typescript; 1 item (Box 104)
    - Volunteer Land Corps, original typescript; 3 items (Box 104)
    - Wagner Act, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 104)
    - War and changing world order, holograph; 13 items (Box 104)
    - War and changing world order, original typescript; 2 folders, 23 items (Box 104)
    - Women, original typescript; 6 items (Box 104)
    - Writers, typescript copy; 4 items (Box 104)
  - Manuscripts - speeches, 1943-1950
    - Arab refugees, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 105)
    - China, original typescript; 4 items (Box 105)
    - Christian spirit, original typescript; 1 item (Box 105)
    - Commencement addresses, typescript copy; 5 items (Box 105)
    - Communism, original typescript; 5 items (Box 105)
    - Constitution, original typescript; 2 items (Box 105)
    - Democracy, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 105)
    - Domestic policy, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 105)
    - Education, original typescript; 5 items (Box 105)
    - Europe, original typescript; 6 items (Box 105)
    - Foreign policy, original typescript; 11 items (Box 105)
    - Freedom, original typescript; 7 items (Box 105)
    - Germany, original typescript; 4 items (Box 105)
    - Jewish question, original typescript; 4 items (Box 105)
    - Journalism, original typescript; 1 item (Box 105)
    - Jacques Martain, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 105)
    - Maxim Kopf, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 105)
    - Middle East, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 105)
    - Mihailovitch, Draja, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 105)
    - Peace movements, original typescript; 5 items (Box 106)
    - Poland, original typescript; 2 items (Box 106)
    - Politics, typescript copy; 3 items (Box 106)
    - Russia, original typescript; 7 items (Box 106)
    - Social responsibility, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 106)
    - War and changing world order, original typescript; 3 folders, 32 items (Box 106)
    - Women, original typescript; 6 items (Box 106)
    - Writers, original typescript; 2 items (Box 106)
  - Manuscripts - speeches, 1951-1961
    - American way of life, original typescript; 2 items (Box 107)
    - Arab world and the Middle East, original typescript; 10 items (Box 107)
    - Arab world and the Middle East, holograph; 16 items (Box 107)
    - Christian spirit, original typescript; 4 items (Box 107)
    - Commencement addresses, original typescript; 1 item (Box 107)
    - Constitutionalism, original typescript; 1 item (Box 107)
    - Domestic policies, original typescript; 3 items (Box 107)
    - Education, original typescript; 6 items (Box 107)
    - Europe, original typescript; 3 items (Box 107)
    - Foreign policy, original typescript; 3 folders, 25 items (Box 107)
    - Internationalism, original typescript; 1 item (Box 108)
    - Jewish question, original typescript; 2 items (Box 108)
    - Journalism, original typescript; 5 items (Box 108)
    - Liberty, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 108)
    - Middle East, original typescript; 1 item (Box 108)
    - Politics, original typescript; 6 items (Box 108)
    - Stalin and Communism, original typescript; 4 items (Box 108)
    - War and the changing world, original typescript; 2 folders, 14 items (Box 108)
    - Women, original typescript; 3 items (Box 108)
    - Miscellaneous, original typescript; 8 items (Box 108)
  - Published speeches and articles
    - Published speeches, 1937-1955; 43 items (Box 109)
    - Published articles, 1920-1930; 20 items (Box 109)
    - Published articles, 1931-1935; 7 items (Box 109)
    - Published articles, 1936-1939; 22 items (Box 109)
    - Published articles, 1940-1945; 30 items (Box 109)
    - Published articles, 1946-1947; 87 items (Box 110)
    - Published articles, 1948; 1950-1952; 73 items (Box 110)
    - Published articles, 1953-1960; 57 items (Box 110)
    - Published articles, undated; 44 items (Box 110)
  - Manuscripts - radio broadcasts
    - Pall Mall broadcast, 1937; 12 items (Box 111)
    - Pall Mall broadcast, 1937-1938; 11 items (Box 111)
    - Pall Mall broadcast, 1938; 27 items (Box 111)
    - NBC, 1939; 32 items (Box 111)
    - Columbia Network, 1938-1940; 11 items (Box 112)
    - General Electric, 1938-1939; 33 items (Box 112)
    - W.O.R. broadcast, 1938-1940; 39 items (Box 112)
    - W.O.R. broadcast, 1941; 35 items (Box 112)
    - Blue Network, Jan-Jun 1942; 16 items (Box 113)
    - Blue Network, Sep-Dec 1942; 13 items (Box 113)
    - Blue Network, Jan-Jun 1943; 14 items (Box 113)
    - Blue Network, Sep-Dec 1943; 21 items (Box 113)
    - Blue Network, 1944; 11 items (Box 113)
    - Blue Network, 1947-1948; 2 items (Box 113)
    - Radio broadcasts, 1951-1952; 2 items (Box 113)
    - German broadcasts, 3 items (Box 113)
    - Town meeting, 7 items (Box 113)
    - Undated and miscellaneous, 7 items (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts
    - Autobiographical
      - "Childhood" holograph notes, 5 items (Box 114)
      - Chapter I, original typescript; 1 item (Box 114)
      - "Childhood", pp. 1-42 original typescript; 1 item (Box 114)
      - "Childhood", original typescript; 14 items (Box 114)
      - "College Days" (and Diary), original typescript; 8 items (Box 114)
      - Sep 1957, pp. 1-3 mimeographed copies; 14 items (Box 114)
      - Letters to Dorothy Thompson regarding autobiography, 40 items (Box 114)
      - Miscellaneous, 17 items (Box 114)
    - Plays
      - "Another Sun" (with Fritz Kortner), typescript copy; 1 item (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun", typescript, first carbon; 1 item (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun", typescript, second carbon; 1 item (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun" Act I and Act II, typescript copy; 9 items (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun" Act III, typescript copy; 5 items (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun" Act III, original typescript; 1 item (Box 115)
      - "Another Sun" proposed changes and outline, typescript copy; 42 items (Box 115)
      - "Cue for Passion", original typescript; 1 item (Box 115)
      - "Cue for Passion", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 115)
      - Spell Your Name (a play) by Dorothy Thompson and Fritz Kortner, original typescript; 1 item (Box 116)
      - Spell Your Name, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 116)
      - Spell Your Name, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 116)
      - Spell Your Name, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 116)
      - Spell Your Name, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 116)
      - Production and financial, 12 items (Box 116)
      - "Patriots", original typescript; 4 items (Box 116)
      - "A Trifling Incident", original typescript; 1 item (Box 116)
    - Novels
      - "As the Hart", pp. 1-69 original typescript; 1 item (Box 117)
      - "As the Hart", pp. 70-142; 1 item (Box 117)
      - "As the Hart", pp. 1-79 first revision original typescript; 1 item (Box 117)
      - "As the Hart", pp. 80-176 first revision holograph notes and original typescript; 4 items (Box 117)
      - "As the Hart", pp. 1-161 typescript copy; 4 items (Box 117)
      - "As the Hart", pp. 1-166 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 117)
      - "The Courage to be Happy", pp. 1-227 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 117)
    - Various fiction and non-fiction
      - "The Boy and Man from Main Street", original typescript; 6 items (Box 118)
      - "Dawn's Early Light" by Dorothy Thompson and Fritz Kortner, typescript copy; 2 items (Box 118)
      - "The Detroit Story", original typescript; 1 item (Box 118)
      - "The Detroit Story" related materials, 8 items (Box 118)
      - "For Love of Cherry Allen", typescript copy; 5 items (Box 118)
      - "The Cordell Hull Story", original typescript; 1 item (Box 118)
      - "I Should Have Murdered Him", original typescript; 1 item (Box 118)
      - "I Try to Think", holograph; 2 items (Box 119)
      - "The Moral Crisis of Our Times", holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "The Moral Crisis of Our Times", original typescript; 2 folders, 5 items (Box 119)
      - "The Moral Crisis of Our Times", typescript copy; 2 items (Box 119)
      - "Statement for the Committee to Develop an Agro-Industrial Foundation", original typescript; 4 items (Box 119)
    - Poetry
      - "As I Lie There ..."), holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "The Fight", holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "The Hermit", original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - ("How Grand It Is ..."), holograph; 2 items (Box 119)
      - ("I, Who Have Seen ..."), holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Just Martyn", holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Larkspur in Starlight", original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Poem in 'The Frankfurter Zeitung'", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Since Zelda Went Away", holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "A Tired Wish", original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - ("Two Candles Made Two Flames ..."), original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "V.", original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Way Down in Old Steuben" by Dorothy Thompson and Laura Moench, holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - ("What Can I Do ..."), holograph; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Women's Day Hymn", published; 1 item (Box 119)
      - "Word Before Parting", original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - ("You Burn, A Hissing Flame ..."), original typescript; 1 item (Box 119)
      - Miscellaneous, including rebuttal to Theodore Dreiser and "Quotable Words", typescript copy; 3 items (Box 119)
- Notes and research material
  - Books
    These books presumably came from Thompson's personal library. The books have numerous annotations, underlining, and marginalia in a hand which looks like Thompson's
    - Belloc, Hilaire / The crisis of civlization, Fordham University Press, 1937 (Box 141)
    - Budenz, Louis Francis / This is my story, Whittlesey House, 1947 (Box 141)
    - Chambers, Whittaker / Witness, Random House, 1952 (Box 141)
    - Conrad, Joseph / The secret agent, Doubleday Page & Co., 1924 (Box 141)
    - Engel, Sophie / La Chine et L'Italie, 1935; custom binding, gold-stamped with Thompson's name and date, pages uncut; signed and inscribed on front free endpaper by author to Thompson (Box 141)
    - George, Henry / Progress and poverty, Robert Schalkenbach Foundation, 1937 (Box 141)
    - Hocking, William Earnest / The coming world civilization, Harper & Brother Publishers, 1956 (Box 142)
    - Keynes, John Maynard / The economic consequences of the peace, Harcourt Brace & Howe, 1920 (Box 142)
    - Lawrence, D. H. / Apocalypse, Albatross Books, 1932 (Box 142)
    - Lea, Homer / The day of the Saxon, Harper & Brother Publishers, 1942 (Box 142)
    - Mounier, Emmanuel / A personalist manifesto, Longmans Green & Co, 1938 (Box 142)
    - Rauschning, Hermann / The redemption of democracy: The coming Atlantic empire, Alliance Book Corporation, 1941 (Box 142)
    - Steiner, Rudolf / The social future, Rudolf Steiner Publishing Co., 1935 (Box 142)
    - Wirsing, Gilselher / Zwischen Europa und die deutsche Zukunft, Eugen Diederichs Verlag, 1932 (Box 142)
  - Notes and research materials by date
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1938-1949; 17 items (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1941; 16 items (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1941-1942; 2 folders, 48 items (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, Undated (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1944; 5 items (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, Undated (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, Undated (Box 120)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1945; 75 items (Box 121)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1946; 62 items (Box 121)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1947; 3 items (Box 121)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1949; 1 item (Box 121)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1951-1952; 44 items (Box 121)
    - Holographs and typescripts, 1955-1956; 1960; 24 items (Box 122)
    - Holographs and typescripts, Undated; 120 items (Box 122)
    - Holographs and typescripts, Undated; 2 folders, 209 items (Box 123)
  - Notes - general subjects
    - A-B, 9 items (Box 124)
    - C, 16 items (Box 124)
    - D, 3 items (Box 124)
    - E, 11 items (Box 124)
    - F, 12 items (Box 124)
    - G, 17 items (Box 124)
    - H, 4 items (Box 125)
    - I-L, 66 items (Box 125)
    - M-N, 15 items (Box 125)
    - P, 11 items (Box 125)
    - R, 17 items (Box 125)
    - S, 3 items (Box 125)
    - T, 6 items (Box 125)
    - U, 2 items (Box 125)
    - V, 4 items (Box 125)
    - W, 10 items (Box 125)
    - X-Z, 1 item (Box 125)
  - Notes and research materials, alphabetical
    - Cairo, research materials, 1950; 16 items (Box 126)
    - England
      - Notes, 1941; 18 items (Box 126)
      - Research materials, 1941; 25 items (Box 126)
    - Europe
      - "Conversation with Fodor", 1960; 19 items (Box 126)
      - Notes, 1940; 29 items (Box 126)
      - Research materials, 1938-1941; 24 items (Box 126)
      - Research materials, 1939-1941; 20 items (Box 126)
      - Notes, 1942; 7 items (Box 126)
      - Notes, 1945; 19 items (Box 127)
      - Research materials, 1945; 62 items (Box 127)
      - Research materials, 1945; 1949-1952; 37 items (Box 127)
      - Notes, 1954-1955; 20 items (Box 127)
      - Research materials, 1953; 1955; 69 items (Box 127)
    - General Labor, 1934; 1936-1937; 6 items (Box 128)
    - Germany
      - Notes, 1942-1943; 1 item (Box 128)
      - Research materials, 1925; 1930-1943; 13 items (Box 128)
      - Notes, 1949; 35 items (Box 128)
      - Research materials, 1941; 1945,; 1949; 20 items (Box 128)
      - Research materials, 1949; 13 items (Box 129)
      - Research materials, 1948; 1949; 11 items (Box 129)
      - Research materials, 1951-1952; 2 folders, 44 items (Box 130)
      - Notes, 1952; 6 items (Box 130)
      - Research materials, undated; clippings; 10 items (Box 130)
    - Greece, research materials, 1949; 13 items (Box 130)
    - India, research materials, 1959; 1 item (Box 130)
    - Italy, research materials, 1949; 3 items (Box 130)
    - Jewish question, research materials, 1958-1959; 12 items (Box 130)
    - Middle East
      - Notes, 1942-1945; 11 items (Box 131)
      - Notes, 1950-1952; 20 items (Box 131)
      - Research materials, 1949-1951; 22 items (Box 131)
      - Research materials, 1952; undated; 32 items (Box 131)
      - Notes, 1956-1957; 95 items (Box 131)
      - Research materials, 1956-1958; 25 items (Box 132)
    - RCA, research materials, 1936; 3 items (Box 132)
    - Sweden and Finland